

About me

I have been in the graphic design industry for almost 3 years. I have work experience at a local outdoor advertising and sportswear company.

I am proficient in Photoshop, Illustrator, and CorelDraw. My skills specialize in print design, jersey and t-shirt design, logo design, and graphic illustration.

Skills & Interests:

- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- CorelDraw
- After Effects
- · SketchUp 3D
- · Graphic Design
- · Video Editing
- · 3D Modeling
- · Social Media marketing
- Coding

- ****
- ^ ^ ^ A
- ^ ^ ^ ^ ^ ^
- ^ ^ ^ ^ /
- ***
- **^ ^ A A A A**
- * * W W Z
- $\star\star \star \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond$

Contacts:

- Zone 2 Bell, Magarao,
 Camarines Sur, Philippines
- 🔀 jayrdelima139@gmail.com
- **(** +639165603070

Viber:



SANDY M DE LIMA

GRAPHIC DESIGNER



WORKING EXPERIENCE

Freelance Graphic Designer

Bisakol outdoor shop (2019-present)

- Create Mockup Design for Sportswear like Basketball Jersey, Cycling Jersey, Uniforms, and outdoor / camping suits.
- Layout the design to the actual pattern and prepare for printing and fabrication.

Graphic Designer, Printer Operator

Golden Touch Advertising (2018-2022)

- Participate client meetings to discuss the project overview, expectations, and completion dates.
- Designing Print Ads for banners, signages, billboards and other print media.
- · Layout and prepare the graphics for the printing and fabrication of the products.
- Finalize the size and color to match the graphics and Print Output
- Print Graphics Media and Maintain the print quality of the products.

Autocad Operator

AB Surveying and Development (2017)

• Creating 3D model in Autocad recap from the 3D scanned data given by the Project Manager.

Intern Graphic designer

Annie Mikka's Printing station (2016)

· Designing and layout templates for print ads.



EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

(Undergraduate)

AMA Computer College, Magsaysay, Naga city 2014 - 2016